emmawatson.com 2008-06-17

# The official website of British actress Emma Watson

Emma Watson (“ **we** ”, “ **our** ”, “ **us** ”) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our Terms and Conditions) sets out the basis on which any personal information that we collect from you or that you provide to us will be processed by us. Please read this policy carefully to understand how your personal data will be treated by us.

1. | MEMBER INFORMATION   
1.1 | When you register as a Member you will be required to provide us with the following information (the “ **Member Information** ”):  
  
1.1.1 | your user name;  
1.1.2 | your date of birth;  
1.1.3 | your email address; and  
1.1.4 | your gender.  
1.2 | If you enter a competition that is run through the Site, we will use your Member Information to contact you in the event that you win a prize and to deliver your prize to you.  
1.3 | We will also use your Member Information to provide any goods or services which you purchase from us.  
1.4 | We may wish to use your Member Information or other personal information you provide to us to provide you with newsletters and other information about Emma Watson or to provide you with information about the products and services of our carefully selected partners. We will only do this with your permission, whether obtained during the registration process or subsequently. If you wish to ask us not to use your personal data for these purposes after permission has been given, please email us at [info@emmawatsonofficial.com](mailto:info@emmawatsonofficial.com) **_._**  
| 2. | CHILDREN UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE  
---|---  
2.1 | If you are under 13 years of age you must get your parent of legal guardian’s consent before registering as a Member. Access to certain areas of the Website may be restricted to users under 13 years of age.  
2.2 | If you are under 13 years of age we will send an email to your parent or legal guardian seeking permission for you to register as a Member. If we do not receive permission, we will suppress any personal data that we have collected from you.  
3. | DATA PROTECTION   
3.1 | As personal data within the meaning of the Data Protection Act 1988 (the “ **Act** ”) we will treat your Member Information and any other personal data which you provide us with through your use of the Website in accordance with the Act.  
3.2 | If your Member Information or any other personal information we collect from you or you provide to us changes you can email us [info@emmawatsonofficial.com](mailto:info@emmawatsonofficial.com) to make changes to that information.  
3.3 | Personal data collected via the Website is controlled by Emma Watson c/o Chris Watson, Dechert LLP, 160 Queen Victoria Street, London, EC4V 4QQ.  
| 4. | STORAGE AND TRANSFER OF INFORMATION  
---|---  
4.1 | We may store your personal data in our databases. We may transfer your personal data to third parties who are employed by us to manage our databases for us.  
5. | LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES  
5.1 | The Website may contain links to and from websites controlled and operated by third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that this privacy policy will cease to apply and the privacy policy applicable to the third party website will apply.  
5.2 | We shall not be responsible for the activities, privacy policies or levels of privacy compliance of any third party website.  
6. | IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES   
6.1 | We may obtain information about how you use the Website by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. Cookies help us to improve the Website and to deliver a better and more personalised service.  
6.2 | You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website.  
6.3 | We may also collect information about your computer including, where available, your IP address and browser type.  
  |    
| 6.4 | Information obtained using the methods specified in this clause above does not identify any individual.   
---|---  
7. | CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY   
7.1 | Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page.
